[{"answer": "Yes, thanks for having me.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "What is your reaction to what's happened?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "Do you still feel the same way given everything we now know?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "To be honest, I was surprised.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Or were you surprised when you saw that trackside interview?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "For me, I just know him on a competitive nature.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "I mean, did you feel you knew the real Oscar or did he keep himself pretty close?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Yes, I would.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "But would you be very shocked if it turned out that Oscar himself had been abusing steroids?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "I haven't had much time to think about that.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "How are you dealing with the millions of women that have been attracted to you since your Olympic appearances?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "Never -- he never went into detail to -- with me about the situation.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Did he ever share anything with you?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "Personally, I don't know.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "And, Blake, finally, I mean, do you think that you'll ever see Oscar run again?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "To be honest with you, that's not up to me.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Do you believe it?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "This is a very unusual case.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "What is your assessment so far?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "From a legal point of view, if it's believed, it is absolutely credible.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "From a legal point of view, would you think it's credible?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "And we don't actually know yet what the other evidence may be.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "There may be some other types of circumstantial evidence as the things that may have led up to this, but ultimately the judge is going to look him in the eye and say, do I believe you?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "All that will come into play, won't it?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "His progression into darkness from a skinny kid, bushy haired, Cub Scout, computer geek.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "What are the main discoveries that you made about Adam Lanza, do you think?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Well, I think if you look at Adam's life, you know, he started off in school.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "And Alaine Griffin, are these warning signs that should have been picked up by any authorities, do you think, or is he one of those that we've seen so many cases of, who slipped below the current radar?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Yes, they all did.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "Did Adam shoot?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, she bears a lot of responsibility.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Should she have done more, do you think, to get him treatment?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Yes, well, \"Hartford Courant\" reporters Dave Altimari and Ed Mahoney today reported that investigators did find news articles that talked about the massacre in Norway.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "And Alaine, tell me more about what we know about how the guns were stored and also tell me, if you can, about this suggestion that he was trying to emulate and indeed compete with and beat other mass shooters including Anders Breivik who killed 77 people in Norway?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we talked to -- one of the thins about Nancy Lanza, she didn't let too many people into her home.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "And in terms of where his mother kept the weapons, what do we know about that?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I feel strongly that way.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Do you go along with that?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "First of all, have you seen the film \"Zero Dark Thirty\"?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I think Kathryn Bigelow makes great movies.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "I found it utterly compelling, but was it realistic?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "I think we'll have to see long-term what effect or impact it will have on our capacity for work and our ability to execute our missions.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "How helpful is that, in reality, to the SEALS and their operations?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "You know, it's a challenging issue.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Well, there are regulations on gun.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "What is wrong ideologically with guns being regulated the same way?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Again, as I look at the places I've traveled in the world -- and I'm with you in that I've traveled to a large number of countries in the world, and a lot of the most dangerous places in the world -- and a lot of those spots are where the civilian populous in the nation isn't armed and they're challenging dangerous places and they're ugly in many ways.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "I just don't get and I am not hearing a coherent why they should be so easily available to the likes of Adam Lanza and the killer in Aurora, to just walk in to Walmart and take one off a wall?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Totally.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "So it is still there, isn't it?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "You still think that?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I won't say quickly.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Don't you feel it's moving quickly?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "You should become a politician.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Which one?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Do I believe him?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "If it is a good show, I love the Oscars.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "The Oscars on Sunday, are you a fan of the Oscars or is it just a load of the whole theatrical drivel, do you think?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "Do you ever fancy hosting it?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "I have a lot of things going on.", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "The dates?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "First of all, 1:00 in the morning, there he is, this is a good time to say you're bisexual, because, you know, 1:00 in the morning, everybody's --", "docId": "130219pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "What is your immediate, very short reaction?", "qSentId": 619}]